Boss, I already saw the people
looking for you.
I'm covering the raid as media.
But since it's official
and government-sanctioned,
civilians are not allowed.
You cannot join the operation.
Your brother-in-law will bring
nothing good to this mission.
Does he know about you?
If he knows,
he won't expose himself.
So it looks like
he still doesn't know yet.
You should leave
before Andrew sees you.
Stop here, Sir.
Sorry, I don't need
the ride anymore.
You just wasted my time.
150,000 Lumen-X pills
are on their way
to Valmora as we speak.
The item?
It's all set, Boss.
Ready for dispatch.
This is a major operation.
The meetup is high value.
Boss, we're here. Have you left?
No, I'm staying.
Let's finish this.
Target site is the
Sanctuary at Valmora.
We're working with the theory
that their deal is with Berdugo.
Dad needs to know
about the transaction.
Where are you, Berdugo?
Orders from Ma'am Delilah
for the guest.
Bring it in.
Let's seal the deal then.
Cheers to new partnerships.
To partnership.
[CLINKS]
Shall we start then?
Andrew is surely still here.
It's risky, he might catch you.
I would prefer you hurry
and start the transaction.
You're in such a hurry.
Why is that?
Could it be those people
chasing you?
They're just small fry
competition.
It needs to be safe,
so you don't have to worry it.
I already told my men to chase
them down and eliminate them.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
- [GRUNTING]
- [THUDDING]
Come on, Team. Let's move!
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Bravo, secure exit.
Alpha, follow me.
Ramos, take the lead.
You too, Andrew, follow me.
The transaction will happen
at Berdugo's villa.
Wait, you'll face
two big syndicates.
And only four of you
will storm in?
It's a quick handoff,
but we still planned it.
The others are nearby,
spread out.
There, look.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Who gave you the right
to interfere in my affairs?
My dear, I was under the
impression that we were a team.
No, Delilah. We are not allies.
We are just businessmen
closing a deal.
That's all.
So now, let's begin
the transaction.
Very well.
[UNEASY MUSIC PLAYING]
Madam, this is ready.
Good.
[CLACKS]
What was that?
[FOREBODING MUSIC PLAYING]
Don't worry.
You're protected.
Protected?
I don't need protection.
Hey!
What are you doing?
Wait.
Why do you look like that?
- [THUDDING]
- [GRUNTING]
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
You really just watched me,
didn't you?
We can't make noise.
Hey!
[GUN FIRES]
[GASPS]
- Boss...
- What was that?
Could it be those people
looking for you?
I thought they were small fry?
- [GRUNTING]
- [THUDDING]
Let's move! Come on.
Anjo, secure Madam.
I'll handle this.
- Boss, let's go!
- Go, Madam.
- I'll take care of this, go on.
- Berdugo, this way.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[GUN FIRING]
- [GOON SPEAKS INDISTINCTLY]
- This way, Boss.
[GUN FIRING]
They shouldn't get away.
[MULTIPLE SHOTS FIRED]
[TIRES SCREECHING]
- [GUN FIRING IN DISTANCE]
- [MULTIPLE SHOTS FIRED]
Let's go!
There's a group moving
towards the parking area.
It could be Berdugo. Intercept!
- [GUN FIRING]
- [TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[GRUNTS]
[TIRES SCREECHING]
Boss!
Hide, Boss! Castro, let's go!
[GUN FIRING]
[GUN CLICKING]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
DDE! Open the door!
[CLACKS]
[GUN FIRING]
[GASPS]
- [GROANS]
- [GUN FIRING]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Zoey, damn you! I trusted you!
I even told you my plans!
You still have time to change,
Francis!
Surrender now!
You're insane!
[GUN FIRING]
You're the ones
who should surrender!
You entered the wrong den!
[GUN FIRING]
[GRUNTS]
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Joey?
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
[THUDS]
What the hell is she doing here?
- [GRUNTING]
- [GROANING]
[THUDDING]
- [THUDS]
- [GROANS]
[GROANING]
[GRUNTING]
[INTENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[GROANS]
[GUN FIRING]
[INTENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [GRUNTING]
- [GROANING]
You poor thing.
No one will help you now.
[INTENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[PANTING]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[THUDS]
Francis Toledo,
you are under arrest!
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
So, Valmora...
If this goes clean,
what happens next?
Pray that it goes well.
And if Berdugo's in a good mood,
then maybe...
maybe he will give you time.
Really?
Maybe is all I get?
That's how his world works.
[PHONE RINGING]
Matias...
The DDE raided the transaction
in Valmora.
The items and money were seized.
What?
Yes, everything's gone.
Boss is wounded.
He says he needs to talk to us.
All right, I'm heading there.
I'm coming with you.
No.
Stay here.
This is not the right time.
[INQUISITIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
[EXHALES]
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
We've lost 500 million pesos,
and your brother-in-law
even shot you.
Let's not focus on the losses,
Matias.
We still have fast-moving items
because of strong demand.
Do you think Andrew
recognized you?
He wouldn't just shoot me
if he knew his brother-in-law
was the one he was chasing.
But he still shot you.
What do we do now?
Let him be.
Let him chase Berdugo.
The more he focuses
on that name,
the less he looks at me.
And men like Andrew...
They don't know when to stop,
and that's what will kill him.
[UNEASY MUSIC CONTINUES]
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Why, Boss?
One of my cufflinks is missing.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Hurry up!
Bring those in!
Are you okay?
Thank you for saving me.
I'm just doing my job.
But if you really want
to repay me,
you could give up Andrew.
Of course, sure.
Relax.
[CHUCKLES]
I'm just joking.
But seriously, I didn't know
you were that good
at fighting, Joey.
My father taught me.
About that...
We didn't get Berdugo
like we wanted.
But at least it's clear he's
the one Delilah is dealing with.
Did we get any identification
on him?
None.
I had the entire resort's CCTV
checked,
but it hasn't been operational
for three days.
It was deliberately done
so there'd be no recording.
Exactly.
But, Joey, you still put
yourself in danger,
along with this operation.
Will I be charged?
Let's just make sure
it doesn't happen again.
It really shouldn't anymore.
Excuse me.
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
What were you thinking, Joey?
You put yourself in the middle
of the firefight again.
- That's...
- Stupid?
Then why don't you finish
saying it?
If I do it, it's stupid?
So, what about the things
you're telling my father?
That I'm resourceful
and good at fighting...
Was that all just a joke?
What I'm saying is you keep
throwing yourself
into danger recklessly.
That's my choice.
A choice you don't need
to understand.
And it's my choice
not to abandon you.
Why do you have to do that?
I made a deal with you
to find Berdugo together.
But nowhere in that deal
did it say
that my life depends on you.
I don't want you
always worrying about me.
always saving me.
What's so wrong with that?
That's why I'm with you,
isn't it?
But you won't always be there.
That's why I don't want
to get used to it.
Why don't you just let me be?
Let me learn.
Let me get hurt
and fight on my own.
Joey, I can't just watch
silently
while you put yourself
in danger.
[ZOEY CLEARS THROAT]
I hope I'm not interrupting,
but I have something to say.
[INQUISITIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
Birthdays, anniversaries,
even simple dinners.
He wants us to have photos
because he says
he wants to capture
how happy we are
in those moments.
Sir Tomas is really sweet.
But, Ma'am, Sir Tomas...
he seems like a very private
person, doesn't he?
Extremely.
Even I don't know everything
he does.
He says that
if I love him enough,
then I should trust him in the
things I don't need to know.
- [CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
- [PHONE RINGING]
Wait.
Hello, Hon?
Okay.
That's good.
Okay, I'll see you.
Hey.
Tomas is coming home,
so I'll talk to nanny to cook,
all right?
- All right.
- See you.
A person who is too private...
often has many things to hide.
So, you heard us, Ma'am.
But...
Ma'am, I'm sorry.
I don't mean to meddle, but...
why don't you tell Ma'am Yvette
if you have a problem
with Sir Tomas?
She wouldn't want to know.
But why?
Why don't you like Sir Tomas?
This ends today, Tomas.
My credibility took decades
to build,
and I refuse to let it rot
like this.
[INQUISITIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
Does it pay better
than practicality?
Yes, of course.
Things money can't buy...
peace of mind, a quiet life,
and most importantly,
the safety of family.
Then let me just remind you,
Rebecca.
It wasn't this network that
gave you safety and comfort.
It was me, Rebecca.
I did my part.
I buried the truths
you wanted hidden.
And I'm done risking
my children's lives
for your operations.
You can't just walk away from
something like this, Rebecca.
Not when you've been
in the circle too long.
You know too much.
Well...
watch me.
And if I don't let you go?
Then...
I'll tell Yvette everything.
Every lie, every drug deal.
Be careful, Rebecca.
Some truths are dangerous
to the one who delivers them.
Are you threatening me?
All I'm saying is, Rebecca...
this world is dangerous.
[GASPING]
[CROWD CLAMORING]
And unfair.
- Andrew!
- [GUN FIRES]
You've made enemies.
And if something
were to happen to you,
they wouldn't be surprised.
So be careful out there.
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
For me.
For Yvette.
And for your grandchildren.
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
Ma'am Rebecca...
are you okay?
Just remember...
do not trust Tomas.
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
Joey, you've been there
all along?
A little while, yes.
So...
do you have any news
from the precinct?
I'm sick and tired
of their excuses
about your father's body.
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
My dear...
My dear, is there a problem?
Remember, I told you
to tell me everything,
especially if you're going
through something difficult.
It's just the two of us now,
so I want us to be okay.
What's wrong?
Nothing, Mom.
I just wanted to tell you
something.
[GATE CREAKING]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING]
The case I'm handling now
is the biggest drug syndicate
in the Philippines.
Berdugo is real.
What's more important?
Andrew or your business?
Nothing matters more to me
than my family and the business
that keeps us alive.
I found this.
There's an engraving.
I need to finish the mission.
I promise, after this mission,
Berdugo will be behind bars.
Was the deal finalized?
Unfortunately, not.
Tomas, is that blood?
Why, Hon?
Where did you get hurt?
I got this.
I'll just change the bandage.
Yvette, it's not just
a small cut.
What do you mean?
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]